faxo.com 2010-06-19

# Faxo - Privacy Policy

Last modified: April 10, 2008 

## Introduction

Faxo respects the privacy of its users. Its Privacy Policy applies to all products, websites, and services offered by Faxo. 

Faxo is registered with the U.S. Department of Commerce’s safe harbor program and abides by its principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, data integrity, security, access and enforcement. 

We hope you will take time to read this policy. Please contact us if you have any questions or comments [here](http://faxo.com/faxo/Contact/) . 

## Personal Data

Faxo guarantees the privacy of your personal information. Personal information is collected and processed for the purpose of offering products and services, to maintain and improve products and services and to assure that the network functions properly. 

  * ## Collection

When you register with Faxo, you are asked for personal information, such as your name, email address, zip code, etc. For some services, you may be asked to provide credit card or alternate payment information, all of which is encrypted on secure servers. Personal information may also be received from our business partners, who must give an absolute guarantee regarding their authorization to transfer that information. 

  * ## Use

As Faxo receives email or other communication from its users, those emails and communications may be stored. Our focus is to use information to improve the quality of our services and to respond effectively and efficiently to requests and inquiries. Some of our services may be offered in connection with other websites. In cases where you provide personal information to those sites, that information may be sent to Faxo for delivery of services. In such cases, we encourage you to be aware of these sites’ privacy policies. Please note that our privacy policy applies only to sites and services under the direct ownership of Faxo. Personal information will not be collected or used for any other purposes than those outlined in Faxo’s Privacy Policy unless prior consent has been given by you. 

  * ## Storage

Throughout the duration of your account, Faxo will store your personal information. If you choose to delete your account, this information will be stored for 90 days after the deletion. The purpose is to secure this data and to avoid exploitation by particular users with malicious intention. 

## Cookies

Small text files that record information about a site visitor are called cookies. Cookies are used by Faxo to improve our search services, storing user preferences and tracking user trends in searching, not to spy on your Internet activity. Most web browsers accept cookies, but you may block them by resetting your browser to refuse cookies. However, if you disable your cookies, some features and services of Faxo may not function properly. 

## Connection Logs

Each time you visit a website, Faxo’s servers automatically record the connection data that your browser send. These logs may include data such as your web search, IP address, browser language, browser type, and cookies that identify your browser. In turn, Faxo will remember your preferences and you will not need to enter those preferences each time you use the search engine. 

## Sharing Personal Information

Faxo will never share your personal data with any third party without your consent. Personal information will only be shared in order that: 

  * Your request for a product or service may be provided,
  * Faxo may provide such information as required by law,
  * Your data may be transferred and stored on different servers for storage and security,
  * Fraud, security or technical issues may be addressed,
  * As permitted by law, Faxo, its users or the general public are protected against imminent harm to rights, property, or safety.

## Security of Personal Data

In order to operate, maintain, and improve Faxo’s services, restricted access to personal data is needed by some of Faxo’s employees and agents. All are bound by confidentiality contract clauses and are subject to disciplinary action for violations. Such disciplinary actions may include reprimands, termination, and criminal prosecution. 

## Access and Update of Personal Data

You have online access to all your personal data. This information can be updated or deleted at any time. Users are asked to identify themselves and data to be accessed, updated, or deleted. Requests may be denied if excessive technical effort or the infringement of others privacy will result. 

## Policy Changes

This Privacy Policy will change, evolving over time. However, your rights as a Faxo user will never be reduced. The effective date of each policy will be posted at the top of the Privacy Policy page. 

## Policy Enforcement

A regular review of Faxo’s policy compliance will be made. If you have suggestions or complaints, contact us [here](http://faxo.com/faxo/Contact/). Complaining users will be contacted regarding concerns. In the situation where a complaint can not be resolved, appropriate regulatory authorities will be utilized.
